n2yo.com 2013-06-01

# Privacy policy

`

##### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which n2yo.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the n2yo.com.com Web Site (each, a "User"). 

##### Privacy

n2yo.com is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to n2yo.com and believes every User should know how n2yo.com utilizes the information collected from the Web Site. 

##### The Information We Collect

n2yo.com may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for setting customized geographic locations, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. n2yo.com may also collect information about how Users use our Web Site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web Site, or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web Site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users' PC and use to identify the User should they visit the web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web Site. We currently use third party ad networks to serve ads on our site. The cookies received with banner ads served by these networks are used to collect and build anonymous behavioral profiles by these companies to deliver targeted ads and tracking referrals, and n2yo.com does not have access to this information. 

##### How We Use Information

n2yo.com does not share the User information collected with any other third party partner or affiliate 

##### Maintenance of Information

Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure. 

For further questions, please [contact us](http://www.n2yo.com/feedback.php)

`

` January 29, 2008 `
